RAIMA

SOULE-FAISANT



raimasoule@gmail.com rsoul004@odu.edu



757 816 7484 /+33652148691



NORFOLK, 23404 VA USA CLAMART, 92140 FRANCE

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Hardworking and passionate with support.

Handling software related issues, troubleshooting software problems and identifying the root causes.

Reviewing work logs and supervising other analysts and technicians. Deliver services and support with a focus on quality and an exceptional experience for customers/end users.

Participate in technical discussions for configuration, testing, and operations of solutions.

Ready to help team achieve company goals, always stay up-to-date on latest technologies.

SKILLS

- Technical Analysis
- Root cause analysis, SQL understanding
- SalesForce, EasyVista, AxCare, Isilog, ServiceNow, RedMine, Jira
- Excellent Communication
- Teamwork & Collaboration
- Self-Motivated
- Problem-Solving
- working with Agile/Scrum, SLA, ITIL
- In-depth knowledge on various OS & software applications
- IIS management, HTML, XML logs
- MS Office
- Install & configure servers & roles: WSUS, AD

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATION

Old Dominion University Norfolk VA • 08/2024 - current Master in Computer Science

OFIEL Formation Paris PARIS • 06/2017

Training & Certification: Microsoft SQL Server 2012 Training Course

 Administration and configuration of SQL Server databases

IPREC Paris
PARIS • 07/2015

Bachelor of Science: Graduate Technician in Systems and Networks

WORK HISTORY

CLARIVATE - Senior Application Support Analyst PARIS • 01/2020 - Current

- Handling software related issues, troubleshooting software problems and identifying the root causes
- Collaborated with upper management to drive strategy and implement new processes
- Performed internal system acceptance to deliver well-tested enhancements and meet business requirements
- Coordinate with various stakeholders to create or improve workflows
- Troubleshot incidents reported by end-users to schedule system changes and identify permanent solutions

WIZTEK - Helpdesk Manager PARIS • 04/2018 - 05/2019

- Management of a team of 8 support technicians
- Responded promptly to requests for technical support
- Recruited, trained and supported help desk technicians and representatives

TRIBVN HEALTHCARE - Software Support Analyst *PARIS* • 03/2015 - 04/2018

- Medical Software support for Scientists, Doctors, laboratory technicians and hospitals
- Provide training to the solutions' end users
- Followed up with clients to verify optimal customer satisfaction following support engagement and problem resolution
- SQL database and application installation

IBS Consulting Paris

PARIS • 11/2014

Training & Certification: Cisco CCNA 200-120 Training & Certification

- Cisco CCNA 200-120 certified
- Routing & Switching, Install and configure Cisco routers

IB CEGOS La Défense

PARIS • 08/2013

Training & Certification: Microsoft MCSA Server 2012 Training Installing and Configuring Windows Server 2012, 70-410

Global Knowledge

PARIS • 05/2013

Training & Certification: Microsoft MCSA Windows 8 Training

- Certified Microsoft MCSA Windows 8
- Configure and administrate Windows 8 MCSA 70-687

INFA

LYON • 07/2005

Training & Certification: Technical Assistance and Remote Consulting

St Joseph

LYON • 07/2004

Bachelor of Science: Computer and

Information Sciences

Lycée Boissy d'Anglas ANNONAY • 06/2002 High School Diploma

KHOLER FRANCE - Systems and Networks Analyst PARIS • 05/2014 - 01/2015

- Technical support: Systems and networks? Outlook, SAP, Kims
- Improved operations through consistent hard work and dedication
- EMEA users incident analysis and resolution

AOS Associés - Systems and Network Analyst PARIS • 02/2014 - 04/2014

- Administered software licensing, purchasing and installation: AutoCAD, SketchUp 8, Outlook, Lync, SharePoint
- Mitigated risk by analyzing complex computer systems to assess vulnerabilities
- Technical support provided to users
- Assets management with GLPI

PROLIVAL - Network and Systems Analyst PARIS • 02/2011 - 02/2014

- Mutualized B 2 B technical support for 150 companies such as: Bacardi, HEC, Chantelle, Devanlay Lacoste, Ingenico, BESV
- Performed system analysis, documentation, testing, implementation and user support for platform transitions
- Conducted system analysis and implementation to maintain and improve computer systems

LANGUAGES & HOBBIES

Fluent French
English professional
Spanish (basic)
Passionate about new technologies, movies, travelling, reading,
Scrabble and roller-skating